<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<language id="44">

	<page id="350007" title="Boardcomp. Sectornames" descr="Names of all sectors (spoken by Boardcomputer)" voice="yes">
		<!--Unknown Sector Nu -> Unclaimed Sector Delta 15-->
		<t id="1021604">{7,1023832} {12,203} {7,50101}{7,50105}</t>
		
		<!--Unknown Sector Gamma -> Unclaimed Sector Eta 8-->
		<t id="1020907">{7,1023832} {12,206} {7,50108}</t>
		
		<!--Unknown Sector Epsilon -> Unclaimed Sector Iota 8-->
		<t id="1020909">{7,1023832} {12,208} {7,50108}</t>
		
		<!--Z Alpha -> unclaimed sector Iota 10 -->
		<t id="1021109">{7,1023832} {12,208} {7,50101}{7,50100}</t>
		
		<!--Unknown Sector Kappa -> US Iota 16-->
		<t id="1021709">{7,1023832} {12,208} {7,50101}{7,50106}</t>
		
		<!--Y Alpha -> US Kappa 6-->
		<t id="1020710">{7,1023832} {12,209} {7,50106}</t>
		
		<!--Unknown Sector Beta -> US Kappa 7-->
		<t id="1020810">{7,1023832} {12,209} {7,50107}</t>

		<!--Y Beta -> US Lambda 6-->
		<t id="1020711">{7,1023832} {12,210} {7,50106}</t>
		<!--Y Gamma -> US Lambda 9-->
		<t id="1021011">{7,1023832} {12,210} {7,50109}</t>
		
		<!--V Alpha -> US Mu 4-->
		<t id="1020512">{7,1023832} {12,211} {7,50104}</t>
		
		<!--V Beta -> US Nu 7-->
		<t id="1020813">{7,1023832} {12,212} {7,50107}</t>
		
		<!--V Delta -> US Nu 8-->
		<t id="1020913">{7,1023832} {12,212} {7,50108}</t>
		
		<!--V Gamma -> US Xi 7-->
		<t id="1020814">{7,1023832} {12,213} {7,50107}</t>
		
		<!--Unknown Sector Alpha -> US Rho-->
		<t id="1020117">{7,1023832} {12,216}</t>
		
		<!--Unknown Sector Delta -> US Tau 11-->
		<t id="1021219">{7,1023832} {12,218} {7,50101}{7,50101}</t>

		<!--Sanctuary of Darkness-->
		<t id="1020514">{7,1023827}</t>

		<!--Guiding Star-->
		<t id="1020515">{7,1023000}</t>

		<t id="1020610">Creditania</t>

		<t id="1020815">Far Point</t>

		<t id="1021106">Blue Storm</t>

		<!--Spires of Elusion-->
		<t id="1021016">{7,30000}</t>

		<!--Twisted Skies-->
		<t id="1021017">{7,30035}</t>

		<!--Magrathea-->
		<t id="1021111">{7,20006}</t>

		<!--Xenon Sector 7-->
		<t id="1021220">{7,30064} {1951,340108}</t>

		<!--Xenon Sector 9-->
		<t id="1021221">{7,30064} {1951,340106}</t>

		<t id="1021306">Overmasters</t>

		<!--Leap of Faith-->
		<t id="1021308">{7,1023805}</t>

		<t id="1021508">Scion Fire</t>

		<!--Prophecy Fulfilled-->
		<t id="1021703">{7,20005}</t>

		<!--Terran Sectors-->
		<t id="50000">Sol</t>
		<t id="50001">Asteroid Belt</t>
		<t id="50002">Prime</t>
		<t id="50003">Eye</t>
		<t id="50004">of</t>
		<t id="50005">Shadow's End</t>
		<t id="50100">0</t>
		<t id="50101">1</t>
		<t id="50102">2</t>
		<t id="50103">3</t>
		<t id="50104">4</t>
		<t id="50105">5</t>
		<t id="50106">6</t>
		<t id="50107">7</t>
		<t id="50108">8</t>
		<t id="50109">9</t>
		<t id="1020513">Heretic's End</t>
		<t id="1020413">{7,50000} {12,200}</t> <!--Sol Alpha-->
		<t id="1020412">{12,204} {7,50001}</t> <!-- Epsilon Asteroid Belt -->
		<t id="1020312">{12,204} {7,50002}</t>
		<t id="1020314">{7,1023816}</t> <!-- Hope's Nemesis -->
		<t id="1020313">The Moon</t>
		<t id="1020213">Earth</t>
		<t id="1020414">{7,1023804}</t> <!-- Antediluvian Ruins -->
		<t id="1021213">{17,5511}</t> <!-- Nikkonofune -->
		<t id="1021212">{17,10771}</t> <!-- Valhalla -->
		<t id="1021211">{7,1023809}</t> <!-- Proteus Prime -->
		<t id="1021313">Aurora</t>
		<t id="1021312">{17,6211}</t> <!-- Soulstar -->
		<t id="1021311">{7,1023821}</t> <!-- Blue Horizon -->
		<t id="1021314">{9,514}.{9,502}.{9,500}. {17,6161}</t> <!-- OCA Headquarters -->
		<t id="1021414">{7,50005}</t> <!-- Shadow's End -->
		<t id="1021415">{17,7001}</t> <!-- Eclipse -->
		<t id="1021416">{7,1023820}</t> <!-- Mists of Artemis -->
		<t id="1020411">{7,50003} {7,50004} {17,3111}</t> <!-- Eye of Colossus -->
		<t id="1020212">{7,1023817}</t> <!-- Anacreon's Kingdom -->
		<t id="1020113">{7,1023831}</t> <!-- Gaian Prophecy -->
		<t id="1020112">{12,217} {17,4061}</t> <!-- Sigma Cluster -->
		<t id="1021514">{7,1023808}</t> <!-- Narayan's Revenge -->
		<t id="1021614">{7,1023814}</t> <!-- Lance's Dominion-->
		<t id="1021613">{17,6331}</t> <!-- Appallox -->
		<t id="1021612">{7,1023807}</t> <!-- The Void -->

		<!--Perpetual Sin, moved due to shitty vanilla placement-->
		<t id="1021513">{7,30023}</t>

	</page>

	<page id="19">
		<!--Y, V, Z sector descriptions part 1-->
		<t id="1">Complaints for years about the crowded and heavily regulated Common Wealth government sectors recently spurred an initiative on behalf of all private trade industries.  The idea was to utilize uncontrolled space as an extension of entrepreneur infrastructure in an effort to increase trade growth for private industry, and as a peripheral benefit, alleviate the burden of the trade commission complaint departments.</t>

		<!--Unknown Sectors description-->
		<t id="1030000">Sector is not recognized in the database.</t>

		<!--V Alpha-->
		<t id="1030512">{19,1}\n\nThe V sectors securement was a rare collaboration between Split and Paranid security and logistics forces.</t>

		<!--Sancutary of Darkness-->
		<t id="1030514">It was a surprise to the entire commonwealth when the Phanon Corporation CEO Zalex Yhulan announced on the GNN that their subsidiary companies would be stationed in this newly discovered sliver of the galaxy.  With little resources or population to speak of, rumours say that the Phanon prefer it this way; a place away from prying eyes and pointed questions.</t>

		<!--Zyarth's Dominion-->
		<t id="1030620">Bordering a dangerous Xenon system, this sector satisfied the glory-seeking Split for many years until the minor skirmishes turned into a fight for survival. Recently, a major Xenon fleet entered the sector, the west gate mysteriously shut-down, cutting off both the supply lines and escape route.  It took months to regain a foothold in the sector, with the tenacious Split rebuilding with surprising renewal.</t>

		<!--Zyarth's Stand-->
		<t id="1030620">With the Xenon approaching, the Split found themselves falling back into this desolate system. Supplies were only delivered by jumpdrive or freighter by ship captains mad enough to brave the Xenon forces.  However, that was a while ago, and Split have short memories.  In conjunction with their neighbours, the colonists have been re-establishing this sector as their home, with little heed as to the possibility of history repeating itself.</t>

		<!--Creditania-->
		<t id="1030610">A high Teladi court official used this sector as an unprecedented arbitration strategy in the mediation between two squabbling medium sized companies.  The premise was a financial strategy battle of wits, and whomever managed to profit most would have emerged the litigation victor.  As both companies managed to surpass all initial expectations of the obscure arbitration, the legal battle was quickly forgotten and healthy trade between both companies is at an all-time high.</t>

		<!--Y Sector Alpha-->
		<t id="1030710">{19,1}\n\nThe Y sectors were mostly initiated by the Teladi Company and Teladi private security.</t>

		<!--Y Sector Beta-->
		<t id="1030711">{19,1}\n\nThe Y sectors were mostly initiated by the Teladi Company and Teladi private security.</t>

		<!--V Beta-->
		<t id="1030813">{19,1}\n\nThe V sectors securement was a rare collaboration between Split and Paranid security and logistics forces.</t>

		<!--V Delta-->
		<t id="1030814">{19,1}\n\nThe V sectors securement was a rare collaboration between Split and Paranid security and logistics forces.</t>

		<!--Far Point-->
		<t id="1030815">The Argon military recently expanded into the previously unknown sector to supplement M148's growing demands.</t>

		<!--V Gamma-->
		<t id="1030913">{19,1}\n\nThe V sectors securement was a rare collaboration between Split and Paranid security and logistics forces.</t>

		<!--Y Sector Gamma-->
		<t id="1031011">{19,1}\n\nThe Y sectors were mostly initiated by the Teladi Company and Teladi private security.</t>

		<!--Blue Storm-->
		<t id="1031106">Recently discovered, the Boron have heralded this peaceful slice of space as the new destination getaway for the upper class.  This of course didn't stop private investment firms from capitalizing on the rich resources this sector has to offer.</t>

		<!--Z Alpha-->
		<t id="1031109">{19,1}\n\nThis Z sector was a venture fronted mostly by Argon security forces.</t>

		<!--Overmasters-->
		<t id="1031306">Slave traders had once used this pocket of space as a rendezvous outpost for trade operations.  As the result of two unknown split families war actions, however, these operations were considered too much of a liability to continue.  Eventually private industry took over, and the sector's trade community flourishes to this day.</t>

		<!--Leap of Faith-->
		<t id="1031308">The Goner had found this sector after years of searching for an unknown relic in a remote area of Third Redemption.  The nature of the relic remains a mystery, but whatever the nature of the found artefact, it motivated the mysterious group to designate this sector somewhat of a natural reservation in the name of the Goner organization.</t>

		<!--Scion Fire-->
		<t id="1031508">Low ranking Paranid priests established this sector several years ago with dreams of establishing a foothold for a new branch of the church.  Financial woes and political errors resulted in the project falling short of its intended goal.  Slowly, private industry seeps into this sector to make the most of what their unlucky predecessors started.</t>

		<!--Antediluvian Ruins-->
		<t id="1030414">Orbiting the large gas giant, the inhabited moon called Alpha is the location of the largest Terran archeological site with many artifacts that witnessed the original colonisation and the Terraformer war.</t>

		<!--Heretic's End-->
		<t id="1030513">Originally discovered and claimed by the Paranid, Heretic's End was used primarily as a remote training area. Since the activation of the gate to Earth in this sector and the massive battle that ensued between the Kha'ak and a combined Terran and Commonwealth force, Terran forces have annexed this sector with little argument from the Paranid. The sector has become a buffer zone between Terran and non-Terran space, patrolled by a large contingent of Terran ships.</t>

		<!--Sol Alpha-->
		<t id="1030413">This sector was established only recently by the USC in an effort to bolster inner Solar system economy with a safe connection to the Commonwealth.</t>
		<!--Spires of Ellusion-->
		<t id="1031016">This sector is a well known resting stop for pirates travelling through this criminal ridden channel of sectors.  Though not as luxurious as some nearby Argon hospitality, this "dump", as it is commonly referred to, provides well sought after respite from bounty hunters and security forces.  The towering run down tenements on this sector's only moon, give Spires of Elusion it's curious name.</t>

		<!--Twisted Skies-->
		<t id="1031017">Neighbouring the Argon sector Interworlds has earned the inhabitants of Twisted Skies a reputation for harbouring some of the most brash and daring of pirate youth.  As Interworlds is frequented by Argon military patrols from neighbouring core sectors, it's said that only reckless gangs dare pillage its stations.</t>

		<!--Magrathea-->
		<t id="1031111">There was a time when this sector was home to a budding Paranid outpost.  Interestingly, not a shot was fired when the Paranid ceded control to pirate groups. Over the years, more notorious criminals and gang activity slowly encroached on the small outpost.  One by one, the citizens of the Paranid empire fled to safer and more comfortable destinations.</t>

		<!--Epsilon Asteroid Belt-->
		<t id="1030412">Located in the outer asteroid belt of the Epsilon Eridani start, the purpose of this sector is to provide raw materials for the colony on Epsilon Prime and the Sol System.</t>

		<!--Epsilon Prime-->
		<t id="1030312">After the USC made a decision to start colonising nearby star systems, this planet terraformed by AGI many centuries ago was the first to be successfuly colonised.</t>

		<!--Proteus Prime-->
		<t id="1031211">Protoplanetary system abundant with raw resources has attracted many prospectors when it was originally discovered.</t>

		<!-- Valhalla -->
		<t id="1031212">Discovered through the use of an unfocused jumpdrive by a young Teladi entrepreneur, this sector was auctioned off to the Terran government. Once Terran control was established, the USC used their knowlege of the gates to connect this system with the existing network.</t>

		<!--Nikkonofune-->
		<t id="1031213">Colonial Authority is using this sector for production of high tech goods and as a resupply point for scout ships searching for new systems.</t>

		<!--Hope's Nemesis-->
		<t id="1030314">Being the closest star to Earth, Proxima Centauri sector was originally planned as the location of the first new colony. However, after the discovery of a dormant Terraformer CPU ship in orbit the colonisation effort was delayed.</t>

		<!--The Moon-->
		<t id="1030313">In past times, Earth's moon was little more than a glimmer of the dreams held within those who gazed upon it. The cratered surface now glittering with countless refineries and bases, few will ever remember it as being anything more than a stepping-stone to the stars.</t>

		<!--Earth-->
		<t id="1030213">The jewel of Sol system and home to mankind, Earth. While many see similarities to the Argon homeworld, Earth holds grace and beauty that few could deny as being anything other than unique. For this and painful historical reasons, the AGI Task Force zealously guards the planet that is slowly becoming an interstellar commerce center.</t>

		<!--Sigma Cluster-->
		<t id="1030112">Undiscovered in the first wave of Terran expansion many centuries ago, this sectors is a constant reminder that there is a lot more out there to be explored.</t>

		<!--Unknown Sector Delta-->
		<t id="1031219">Not much is known about this empty portion of space, except that the presence of an ominous Xenon gate gives a solid explanation of why it remains unclaimed.</t>

		<!--Xenon sector 7-->
		<t id="1031220">It was only until recently that exploration began in this sector.  When reports that Xenon stations were spotted within, a Teladi stock market crash resulted in the loss of billions of credits from daring investors with hopes and dreams set on a new frontier.</t>

		<!--Xenon sector 9-->
		<t id="1031221">No ships have entered this sector since the disappearance of an Argon expeditionary force two years ago. Their final report, made in haste and mostly unintelligible, held ominous hints of a xenon shipyard.</t>

		<!--Blue Horizon -->
		<t id="1031311">Home to the most populated planet in all Terran colonies, this system is also the center of industry and inovation for the entire cluster.</t>

		<!--Soulstar-->
		<t id="1031312">This system is believed to have once belonged to the Kha'ak, however the circumstances of their departure are unknown.</t>

		<!--Aurora-->
		<t id="1031313">One of the first colonies to be established before the Terraformer war, the rediscovery of this system is considered as a good omen in the eyes of many deep space pilots.</t>

		<!--OCA Headquarters-->
		<t id="1031314">The USC Office of Colonial Authority was established in this system and is considered by many as the capital of all Terran colonial sectors.</t>

		<!-- Eye of Colossus -->
		<t id="1030411">Named after a brown dwarf that dominates the skies of this newely established Terran colony, this sector is mostly known as the "poster-colony" for USC Colonial Authority.</t>

		<!-- Gaian Prophecy -->
		<t id="1030113">Post-nuclear wasteland of the Split homeworld and it's moons is a warning to everyone of how vicious the Split can get. So far the Split have completely ignored the rediscovery of their original homeworld by the USC.</t>

		<!--Shadow's End-->
		<t id="1031414">A former Kha'ak sector "liberated" in Operation Final Fury, this sector was abandoned by Argon after military operations were finalised because it was too far from any Argon sector.</t>

		<!--Eclipse-->
		<t id="1031415">The Terran Tourism office was surprised with many visa requests from Commonwealth sitizens wanting to enjoy the sights of this dual eclipse sector.</t>

		<!--Mists of Artemis-->
		<t id="1031416">On the very edge of Terran space, this remote sector is the location of many USC radio telescopes searching for distant gates and other phenomena.</t>

		<!--Anacreon's Kingdom-->
		<t id="1030212">One of many sectors to be first colonised before the Terraformer War, this system bears the scars of its time.</t>

		<!--Perpetual Sin-->
		<t id="1031513">This sector, when discovered by the Paranid, was awash with Kha'ak. Paranid forces had daily skirmishes with them until one day, the Kha'ak completely disappeared from the sector, never to be seen there again.</t>

		<!--Narayan's Revenge-->
		<t id="1031514">Name of this system is a memorial to the USC 3rd Fleet flag ship in the battle with combined Argon and Paranid forces.</t>

		<!--The Void-->
		<t id="1031612">This featureless sector is a one of few sectors where USC and ATF allow open trade with Commonwealth races.</t>

		<!--Appallox-->
		<t id="1031613">Regular skirmishes between the Paranid and USC are happening here so often that the Teladi have tried buying broadcasting rights for these "events".</t>

		<!--Lance's Dominion-->
		<t id="1031614">This is a former Split mining colony conquered in an suprise assault by USC Fleet Commander Stevron Aurius Lance. Instead of invading the system directly, Lance used a small fleet of captured Boron ships to attack another Split sector. Once the Split moved their forces to defense positions against the "Boron" ships, Lance jumped the decoys to this sector and blocked the Split from comming back.</t>


	</page>

</language>